ashome.com 2010-06-24

# Privacy Policy for American Signature

##### American Signature Furniture® Internet Privacy Statement

American Signature Furniture respects your right to privacy. We are committed to using any information you give us in a responsible manner. This policy summarizes what personally identifiable information we may collect, and how we might use this information. This policy also describes other important topics relating to your privacy. We suggest that you review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it from time to time.

##### Information Collection

When you become a registered user of this site, we may collect preferences and personal information to make your browse experience as a registered user as quick and easy as possible. To help us better understand how visitors use our site, we collect information on the Internet via cookies and clickstream technology _cookies and clickstream technology_ : A cookie is a small data file or piece of information that is sent by a web site or email and stored on your hard drive. A cookie holds information that our web site and emails may use to create a more personalized browse/shop experience for visitors to our site.

American Signature Furniture (or Value City Furniture) uses a third party to place cookies on your computer to collect on personally identifiable information.

You may choose to set your web browser to not accept cookies. If your cookies are disabled, you can still view our site, but you will not be able to create an account, or benefit from certain services and promotional offers available through our site.

Our web server automatically collects clickstream information such as the address of the web site that you came from before visiting our site, which pages you visit on our site, and other information. This anonymous clickstream data helps us to understand how visitors use our web site.

.

There may be times at which we ask you to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, birth date, gender, occupation, personal interests, etc. Whether or not to provide such information is completely your own choice. But if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to benefit from certain services and/or promotional offers through our web site. 

##### Use of Information

We may use the personally identifiable information you voluntarily provide for internal purposes, such as analyzing trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services and offers, and providing you with information from and about American Signature Furniture. From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours. These are known as our strategic partners. In such cases we might share and cross-reference information, including personally identifiable information about you, that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online and in our stores. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our strategic partners and others. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes. 

##### Updating Information and Opt-Out Feature

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you would prefer not to be contacted, please let us know by removing the check mark from the "Send me exclusive American Signature Furniture email updates" option, which is located on the New Registration and Update Registration page.

If you have already registered with our web site and would like to update your email address, street address or other personal information, please sign in with your user name and password and click the Update link on the My Profile page. 

##### Children and Parents

American Signature Furniture does not intend to collect personally identifiable information from individuals under age of 13 without permission of the individual's parent or legal guardian. Children under the age of 13 should submit personally identifiable information to American Signature Furniture only with the explicit permission of their parent or legal guardian. If your child has submitted personal information and you would like to request that such information be removed, you may do so as indicated above and American Signature Furniture will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request.

##### Other Important Information

The American Signature Furniture web site may contain links to other sites. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. Additionally, some of our web pages may contain "cookies," which are data that may be sent to your web browser and stored on your computer. This allows our server to "recognize" you when you visit our web site to provide you with ease of use and convenience. Most web browsers can be configured to not accept cookies, or to notify you if a cookie is sent to you. It may be necessary, if required by law or if pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations, to release your personally identifiable information.

##### Changes to Site and Consent

Efforts to bring new services, ideas and partners to benefit our customers may make it necessary to amend our Privacy Policy. If this occurs, we will post the new policy on our web site. Once posted the new policy will go into effect immediately, replacing the previous policy. Your use of this site after a change in the Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the change.

##### Your Feedback

To help us improve our Privacy Policy and practice we need your feedback. Please use our Contact Us page by submitting any comments or questions and we will do our best to answer them.

Last modified: 11.28.07
